Eric Rion

5319 Aurora Ct. • Lilburn, Ga • 30047 **CELL** (404) 542-6049 • **E-MAIL** erion42@gmail.com

PROFILE

A lifelong gamer with over a decade of excellent customer service experience, adept at interpersonal interactions between both clients and co-workers, looking for a fulfilling job that challenges while providing room for personal growth and career advancement

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Arts

Psychology(Major)/Sociology(Minor) Georgia State University, Atlanta GA 2011

SKILLS

CompTIA A+ Certification

Hardware/Software Troubleshooting Microsoft and Google Office Suites

Customer Service

Experienced with Windows 10, Macintosh OSX, and distributions of Linux Experience with League of Legends and similar MOBA games

EXPERIENCE

Data Media Associates 2013 - Present

As Strategic Account Manager I create and service accounts that print and mail medical bills. This involves personal health information so an eye for fine details is required. In addition to troubleshooting accounts and providing empathetic customer service for various levels of technical expertise I have also become proficient in various programming languages and have been working remote full-time since the pandemic began so I have experience managing my workflow.

CDC Federal Credit Union 2012 - 2013

As a teller I performed customer service roles such as record keeping, account troubleshooting, routine transactions, and account management. For a time I was also the Vault Teller which required a higher degree of responsibility.

Titan Games and Comics 2008 - 2012

I performed sales and customer service responsibilities as well as store maintenance and event organization. In addition I ordered store product for customers and established friendly working relationships with customers in order to increase their satisfaction with the store and its products.